{
    "categories": [],
    "description": "Name the musical acts who performed these hits from the 2000's.",
    "difficulty": -1,
    "questions": [{
        "answer": "Lady Gaga",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2008 - Poker Face"
    }, {
        "answer": "Beyonc√© Knowles",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2008 - Single Ladies (Put a Ring on It)"
    }, {
        "answer": "Justin Timberlake",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2006 - SexyBack"
    }, {
        "answer": "Green Day",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2004 - American Idiot"
    }, {
        "answer": "Amy Winehouse",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2006 - Rehab"
    }, {
        "answer": "Avril Lavigne",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2002 - Sk8er Boi"
    }, {
        "answer": "Gwen Stefani",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2005 - Hollaback Girl"
    }, {
        "answer": "Kelly Clarkson",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2004 - Since U Been Gone"
    }, {
        "answer": "Outkast",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2003 - Hey-Ya!"
    }, {
        "answer": "Kanye West",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2005 - Gold Digger"
    }, {
        "answer": "Jay-Z",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2004 - 99 Problems"
    }, {
        "answer": "Eminem",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2000 - Stan"
    }, {
        "answer": "Coldplay",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2000 - Yellow"
    }, {
        "answer": "Taylor Swift",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2008 - Love Story"
    }, {
        "answer": "Shaggy",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2001 - It Wasn't Me"
    }, {
        "answer": "U2",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2000 - Beautiful Day"
    }, {
        "answer": "Kings of Leon",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2008 - Sex on Fire"
    }, {
        "answer": "Adele",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2008 - Chasing Pavements"
    }, {
        "answer": "Gorillaz",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2005 - Feel Good Inc."
    }, {
        "answer": "M.I.A.",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2008 - Paper Planes"
    }, {
        "answer": "John Mayer",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2002 - Your Body is a Wonderland"
    }, {
        "answer": "Franz Ferdinand",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2004 - Take Me Out"
    }, {
        "answer": "The White Stripes",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2002 - Fell in Love with a Girl"
    }, {
        "answer": "The Strokes",
        "category": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
        "question": "2001 - Last Nite"
    }],
    "quizLength": 24,
    "title": "Who Did That 2000's Song",
    "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/who-did-that-2000s-song-quiz.php"
}